Finding Aid for the The Donald Grady Davidson Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- General Correspondence
  - Correspondence --Incoming
    - Fletcher, J. G., [March 1935] - [December 17, 1937] (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Fletcher, J. G., [1938, 1942, 1948] (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fletcher, J. G., [1949 - Jan. 1950] (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fletcher, J. G., Feb. 1950 - N. D.'s & Letter to Allen Tate (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fletcher, J. M. - Flint (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Flournoy - Forbes, E., [Jan. 1924] (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Forbes, E. [Feb. 1924... ] - Ford, Jesse Hill (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Ford, Jesse Hill, [Oct. 5, 1960 - 1963] (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fore - Fox, Julia (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Fox, Stuart - Fraser (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Frazer - Frederick, [1936] (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Frederick, [1937-40] (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - French (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Freidlander - Gailor (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Gale - Gates (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Gaus - Gay, [June 1931 - 1935] (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Gay [1936.. .] - Gilchrist (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Gilmore - Gohdes (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Goldgar - Gosnell (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Govan - Gower (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Gower [1956] - Graves, Louis (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Graves, R. - Green-Leach (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Greenslet, 1923 -27] [1933 - March 1938 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Greenslet, March 1938 -1940] - Greig [1931 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Greig [1932] - Guthum (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - H. E. D. - Hafley (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Haile - Hall (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Halland - Handley (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Hans - Hart (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Hartman - Hatcher (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Haun, July 15, 1939 - March 1940 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Haun, May 10, 1940 - Dec. 1947, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Havell - Heisler (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Hellweg - Henslee, Feb. 1947 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Henslee [May 1947.. .] - Hewlings (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Heyward - Hibbard, Aug. 1923 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Hibbard, September 1923 -1925 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Hibbard, 1926 - 1929 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Higgins - Hood (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Hopkins - Howard (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Howe, 1938 - 39 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Howe, Feb. - March 17, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Howe, March 20 - June 1939 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Howe, July 1939 - 1940] - Hubbell[... July 1954 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Hubbell, 1929 - 1957] - Hudson [ 1928 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Hudson, 1936 - 1968 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Hughes - Hyde (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Ijames - Irwin (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Jackson - Jarrell (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Jensen - Johnson, Allen (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Johnson - Johnstone (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Jones, Betty - Jones, Howard M., ... 1929 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Jones, Howard M. [ 1930-38 & Letter to Ransom] - Jones, Madison (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Jones, W. Powell - Kaub, ... May 1948 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Kaub [June 1948.. .] - Keister (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Keller - Kent, ... April 1938 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Kent [May 1938... ] - Kilvington (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Kimball - Kirk, ... July 1955 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Kirk, ... 1955] - Kirkland, J. H. [... 1937 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Kirkland, W. - Kline, .. .1929 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Kline, April 27, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Kline, ... June 2, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Kline [June 2 - June 16, 1930] (photocopies) (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Kline, June 13 - Sept. 1930 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Kline, …1940] - Knickerbocker [... Feb. 1928 to Davidson (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Knickerbocker, .. .1934 to Davidson & 1930 to Ransom (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Knight (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Knott - Kroll (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Kronenberger - Kuhn (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Lacy - Lea (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Leake - Leighton (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Leite - Linscott, ... April 1927 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Linscott [... 1938 & to Tate] - Littlejohn (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Livingood - Lord, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Lord [1939 - 40] - Lowrey (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Lowry - Lyons (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Lytle, 1926 -41 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Lytle, 1942 - 1959 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Lytle, 1961 - 65, N. D.'s (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - McBryde - McClure (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - McCord - Mc Dowell (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - McElfatrick - McIntyre (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - McKeithan - Macrae (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Madden - Martin, H. T., Jan. - Feb. 1923 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Martin, H. F. [April, 1923 - 1931] - Masters (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Mathis - Mellen (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Melton - Merrifield (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Metcalf - Millet (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Mills - Milton, March - August 1930 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Milton, September 1930 - February 10, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Milton, Feb. 18, 1931 - Feb. 12, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Mims, E.[July 19, 1919 - 1949] (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Mims [undated] - Moch (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Modern Age: A Quarterly Review; Eugene Davidson, Richard Weaver, David Collier, Et Al, Outgoing and Incoming, 1960 - 1966 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Moe - Moore, Mary Daniel (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Moore, Merrill, 1924 -1931 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Moore, Merrill, 1932 - 57 & No date (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Moore, R. - Morgan (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Morrilot - Morrison, 1931 -Jan. 19,1934 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Morrison, Jan. 31,1934 - 1938 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Morrison, 1939 -61 and no year (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Morton - Mosely (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Moses, B., 1928 - 30 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Moses, B., 1931 - 39 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Moses, Eliz. - Moses, W. R. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Moss - Mynders (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - N - Nerber [1953 - 1954 ] - Neuman (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Newman - Nixon[1928 - Feb. 13, 1930] (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Nixon[Feb. 21 - March 25, 1931] (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Nixon, March 29,1931 - 1934 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Noble - Nye (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Ochs - O'Donnell, 1935 - Feb. 1938 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - O'Donnell, Feb. 1938 - 1939 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - O'Donnell, 1940 - 1928 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - O'Donnell [1954 & Letter to Tate] - Oglesby (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Oliphant, May, Jan. 22, 1952 - 1961 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Oliphant, May[1962 - Dec. 14, 1965] (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Oliphant, May, Jan. 1966 - Nov. 1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Oliphant, May, Summer 1967 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Olmstead - Olney, 1952 - 55 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Olney [N.D.'s] - Oman (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Oppegard - Owen, H. G., 1931 - 37 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Owen, H. G., 1938 - 54 & N. D.'s (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Owsley (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - P - Paris (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Parker - Parks, E. W., 1933 - 1935 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Park, Edd Winfield, 1936 -39, 1962, & N. D.'s (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Parrigin - Patton (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Payne, T. H. Co., - Pedigo (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Peery - Percy, 1923 - 24 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Percy, 1928 -31 & N.D.] - Peter [1930 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Peter, 1931] - Pettee [1950 - Sept. 1961 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Pettee, October - December 1961 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Pettee, Jan. - June 1962 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Pettee, July - November 1962 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Pettee, Dec. 1962 - Feb. 1963 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Pettee [March - April 1963 & N. D.] - Phillips, James (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Phillips, U. - Pickup (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Pinckney - Pipkin (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Pitts - Pockwinse (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Poe - Porter, H., 1934 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Porter, H. [1935 - 37] - Porter, Richard (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Potamkin - Powell (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Powers - Prisk (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Puckett - Quinn (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Random House and Knopf (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Rankin - Ransom, H. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Ransom, John Crowe, 1927 - 45 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Ransom, John Crowe, 1951 - N.Y,'s (Aug.) (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Ransom, John Crowe, N.Y.'s (Sept.) - N. D.'s (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Ransom, Marie Howe - Reagan (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Reed - Reichert (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Reid - Rice (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Rice - Richardson (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Riding, March - November 1924 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Riding, December 1924 -1927 & N. Y.'s (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Riding, N. D.'s (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Riding, N. D. ‘s (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Riding, N. D.'s (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Riggs - Rinehart, F. R., 1928 -47 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Rinehart, F. M. [1948 -54] - Rinehart S. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Rippey - Robertson (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Robins - Robinson, F. A., 1931 - March 1954 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Robinson, F. A. [ April 1954 - Sept. 1956 ] - Rockwell (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Rodes - Roller (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Romeike - Rosenbaum (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Rosenthal - Rothrock (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Rothschild - Rubin, 1950 -51 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Rubin, 1952 - Dec. 1954 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Rubin, Jan. - April 1955 - Jan. 1961 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Rubin [May 1967 - July 1967, N. D.'s] - Rynn (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - St. Clair - Sanborn (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Savage - Schneider, Lois (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Schneider, J. T. - Scott, D. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Scott, F. A. - Selby, 1945 - Aug. 46 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Selby [Sept. 46 - 48] - Seymore (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Shackelford - Shafer, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Shafer, March - June 1935 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Shafer, July - 1935 - June 1942 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Shannon - Shaw (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Sherer (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Sherrer - Shipley, 1923 -1935 & N. D.'s (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Shively - Simmons (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Simms, William Gilmore. Voltmeier Project. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Simms, William Gilmore, 1950 - 52 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Simpson, C. - Smith, P. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Smith, R. - Spencer, E. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Spencer, W. E. - Stegner (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Stein - Stephens, E., 1938 - 1940 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Stephens, H. - Stevenson, A., 1933 - 46 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Stevenson, A., 1958 -63] - Stewart, E. [1935 - May 36 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Stewart, E., June 1936 - 37] - Stewart, R. [1931 - Feb. 1954 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Stewart. R..[May 1954 - 1960] (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Stix - Stone, G., 1936 - May 1938 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Stone, G., July 1938] - Stuart, Jesse [March - May 1933 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Stuart, Jesse, Sept. 1933 - 1937 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Stuart, Jesse, Oct. 21, 1937 - Feb. 1938 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Stuart, Jesse, 1938 -42 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Stuart, Jesse, Oct. 1942 - Nov. 1952 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Stuart, Jesse, April - Sept. 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Stuart, Jesse, Oct. - Dec. 13, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Stuart, Jesse, Dec. 17, 1953 - June 1, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Stuart, Jesse, June 30, 1954 - May 16, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Stuart, Jesse, May 20, 1955 - 1958 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Stuart, Jesse, Jan. - July 1954 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Stuart, Jesse, Sept. - Oct. 23, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Stuart, Jesse, Oct. 25, 1959 - 1960 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Stuart, Jesse, 1961 - March 12, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Stuart, Jesse, April 1962 - August 1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Stuart, Jesse, Sept. 1967, 1968 & no dates (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Stuart, N. d. - Tarleton (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Tate, Allen, June - July 5, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Tate, Allen, July 12, 1922 - August 17, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Tate, Allen, August 31, 1922 - June 16, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Tate, Allen, June 22, 1923 - July 1923 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Tate, Allen, Aug. 1923 - March 1, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Tate, Allen, March3 -27, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Tate, Allen, April 1924 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Tate, Allen, May 1924 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Tate, Allen, June - Sept. 4, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Tate, Allen, Sept. 11 - Oct. 10, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Tate, Allen, Oct. 11 - Nov. 7, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Tate, Allen, Nov. 9 - Dec. 11, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Tate, Allen, Dec. 17, 1924 - Jan. 1925 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Tate, Allen, Feb. - May 21, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Tate, Allen, May 25 - July 13, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Tate, Allen, July 25 - Oct. 1925 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Tate, Allen, Nov. 1925 -March 3, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Tate, Allen, March 11 - June 1926 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Tate, Allen, July - Sept. 1926 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Tate, Allen, Oct. 1926 - Jan. 1927 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Tate, Allen, Feb. - May 5, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Tate, Allen, May 13 - June 11, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Tate, Allen, June 22 - July 1927 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Tate, Allen, Sept. - Nov. 1927 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Tate, Allen, Jan. - March14, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Tate, Allen, March 16, - April 1928 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Tate, Allen, May - October 1928 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Tate, Allen, Feb. - July 1929 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Tate, Allen, Aug.- Nov. 1929 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Tate, Allen, Dec. 1929 - Feb. 3, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Tate, Allen, Feb. 9 - 27, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Tate, Allen, June - July 1930 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Tate, Allen, Aug. - Nov. 1930 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Tate, Allen, Dec. 1930 - 1931 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Tate, Allen, Jan. - June 1932 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Tate, Allen, Oct. 1932 - March 1933 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Tate, Allen, April 1933 - 1934 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Tate, Allen, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Tate, Allen, Jan. 1936 - April 1937 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Tate, Allen, May 1937 - August 1938 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Tate, Allen, Oct. 1938 -39 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Tate, Allen, Jan. 1940 - June 1942 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Tate, Allen, Aug. 1942 - Feb. 11, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Tate, Allen, Feb. 20, 1943 - Dec. 1950 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Tate, Allen, 1951 - 53 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Tate, Allen, August 1955 - January 1962 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Tate, Allen, Feb. 1962 - Jan. 1963 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Tate, Allen, Feb. 1963 - Jan. 1965 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Tate, Allen, Feb. - Jan. 67, Sept. 1971 & N. D.'s 1924- 30 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Tate, Allen, Jan. - Nov. 14, N. Y.'s (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Tate, Allen, Nov. 18 - Dec. N.Y.'s - N. D.'s & letter to Mims (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Tate, Caroline - Taylor, Tyre (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Taylor, Warren (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Taylor, Wesley F. - Thomas, W. E., 1935 - Feb. 36 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Thomas, W. E. [ April 1936 - 38] - Thompson, C. W. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Thompson, E. - Titterton, 1928 -29 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Titterton [1930] - Todd (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Toledano - Trawick (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Tribble - Tyler (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Underwood - Untermeyer, 1923 - Aug 1926 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Untermeyer [1929 -61 & N. D.] - Upson (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Valentine - Van Doren, Feb. 1925 - Feb. 1927 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Van Doren ,Mark, Oct. 1929 - 1938 ] - Vinal [1924 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Vinal [N. Y. ‘s - N. D. ‘s] - Waddell (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Wade, A. - Wade, James P. (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Wade, John Donald, 1930 - Aug. 1932 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Wade, John Donald, Sept. 1932 - Feb. 1933 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Wade, John Donald, May 1933 - Jan. 9, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Wade, John Donald, Jan. - March 1934 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Wade, John Donald, April 1934 - June 1935 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Wade, John Donald, August 1935 - April 1936 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Wade, John Donald, May 1936 - 1939 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Wade, John Donald, 1940 -Jan 12, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Wade, John Donald, Nov. 1943 - March 1945 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Wade, John Donald, April 1945 - Jan. 1947 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Wade, John Donald, May 1947 - April 1948 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Wade, John Donald, May 1948 - March 1949 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Wade, John Donald, April - Nov. 1949 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Wade, John Donald, Dec. 1949 - July 1951 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Wade, John Donald, Aug. 1951 - 1952 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Wade, John Donald, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Wade, John Donald, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Wade, John Donald, Jan. - April 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Wade, John Donald, May - Dec. 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Wade, John Donald, 1956 - Oct. 1957 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Wade, John Donald, Aug. 1958 - Aug. 1959 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Wade, John Donald, Sept. 1959 - March 1960 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Wade, John Donald, May 1960 - Dec. 6, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Wade, John Donald, Dec. 12, 1960 - April 1961 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Wade, John Donald, May - Oct. 1961 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Wade, John Donald, Nov. 1961 - Jan. 1962 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Wade, John Donald, Feb. - May 1962 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Wade, John Donald, Oct. 1962 - 63 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Wagner - Walker, E. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Walker, L. - Walsh, T., 1937 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Walsh, T., Jan. - June 1938 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Walsh, T., July 27, 1938 - Dec. 14, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Walsh, T., Dec. 28, 1938 -April 1939 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Walsh, T., May - Sept. 1939 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Walsh, T., Oct. 1939 - 1940 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Walsh, T., 1942 - Sept. 9, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Walsh, T., Sept. 14, 1953 - Feb. 1954 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Walsh, T., March - Dec. 9, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Walsh, T., Dec. 10, 1954 - March 1955 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Walsh, T., April 1955 - Aug. 1956 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Walsh, T., Sept. 1956 - Jan. 1957 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Walsh, T., March - May 1957, N. Y. - N. D.] - Ward [1959 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Waring - Warren Mary Celia (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, 1923 -July 1926 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, Sept. 1926 - June 1930 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, Sept. 1930 - 1935 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, 1936 -38 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, 1946 - 62 & N. D. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, N. D.'s (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Warrick - Watt (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Weaver, Bennett (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Weaver, Richard M. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Webb - Weeks (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Weiss - Wells (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Wells - Wheatley, July - Aug. 1928 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Wheatley, Sept. 1928 - March 1954 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Wheeler - Wheelock, 1927 - 1960 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Whitaker - Wieck (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Williams, A - Williams, L (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Williams, O. - Wills, Ellen (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Wills, Jesse, July - Aug. 5 1923 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Wills, Jesse, Aug. 10, 1923 - 1961 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Wills, Ridley (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Wilson, E. - Wilson, L. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Wilson, M. - Winton (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Wise - Woods (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Woody - Wright (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Writer's Monthly - Yarbrough, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Yarbrough [1934 -1935] - Young, F. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Young, J. P. - Young, Stark, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Young, Stark, 1930 - 1931 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Young, Stark, 1934 - 37 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Young, Stark, 1939 - 1952 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Young, Stark, 1953 - 1957 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Young, Stark, 1930, no date (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Young, Stark, 1930, no date (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Young, Stark, N.D. (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Young, Stark, N. D.'s (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Young, Stark, N. D.'s (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Young, Stark, N. D.'s (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Young, Stark, N. D.'s (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Young, Stark, N. D.'s (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Copies of Stark Young Letters Given by Dr. John Pilkington (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Youngstrom - Zugsmith (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Fragments, Unidentified (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Misc. fragments, unidentified, 1930 - 1939 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Fragments, unidentified, 1940's: '42, '44, ‘47 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Misc. fragments, unidentified, 1950's: '52,'56 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Fragments, unidentified, 1960's: '60, '62, '67, ‘68 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Misc. fragments, unidentified-no dates (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Writings
  - Book Manuscripts
    - American Composition and Rhetoric- Introduction (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric No. 1 -No. 29 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric- No. 30- No. 36 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric- No. 30- No. 36 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric- No. 30- No. 36 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric- No. 30- No. 36 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric- No. 30- No. 36 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric- No. 30- No. 36 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric- No. 30- No. 36 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric mss (fragment) (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - American Composition and Rhetoric mss (fragment) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Big Ballad Jamboree (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Big Ballad Jamboree (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Big Ballad Jamboree, Chapters I - VIII, original typed MS (Box 18, Folder 12)